<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Areas on Shadow of the End</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Areas on Shadow of the End</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Secret places</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Secret-places/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Secret-places/</guid>
      <description>Secret places are locations that are hidden or not easily accessible. These could be underground bunkers, hidden rooms in abandoned buildings, or hidden tunnels. They may contain valuable resources or information that could be useful to the player. These places could also be guarded by powerful enemies or traps, making them challenging to explore.&#xA;Hidden bunkers Underground labs Secret military bases Hidden religious sanctuaries </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Camps</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Camps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Camps/</guid>
      <description>Camps are temporary settlements that are set up by various factions or groups of survivors. These camps are often located in the wilderness and are used as a base of operations for scavenging, hunting, and other activities. The camps are usually guarded by a few members of the faction or group and may have basic amenities such as shelter, fire pits, and storage for supplies. The camps are often targeted by hostile factions or creatures and are therefore not considered safe for long-term living.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cities</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Cities/</guid>
      <description>Cities would be areas where can buy and sell items, and access various services such as crafting and training. These cities would be run by different factions, such as The Synthetic Order, The Resilient, and The Devoted. Each city would have its own unique layout, buildings, and inhabitants, reflecting the characteristics and values of the faction that controls it. In addition to providing a safe haven for the player, cities would also serve as hubs for various quests and missions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Old infrastructures</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Old-infrastructures/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Old-infrastructures/</guid>
      <description> Power plants Water treatment facilities Communication towers Transportation hubs </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Wild lands</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Wild-land/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/Locations/Areas/Wild-land/</guid>
      <description>Wild lands are areas of uninhabited by civilization, and are therefore dangerous to explore. These areas can be found in each of the biomes, and are typically inhabited by powerful enemies and hidden treasures. Need to be well-equipped and cautious in order to survive the dangers of the wild lands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
