<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Backstory on Shadow of the End</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/Lore-History/backstory/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Backstory on Shadow of the End</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/Lore-History/backstory/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Devoted</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/Lore-History/backstory/devoted/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/Lore-History/backstory/devoted/</guid>
      <description>In the era before The Dark Fever ravaged the world, a small but fervent religious cult known as the Devoted existed on the fringes of society. They believed that humanity had strayed far from the path laid out by their divine creators, becoming enslaved to technology and materialism rather than living in harmony with nature and spirituality.&#xA;The world they inhabited was one of decadence and depravity, a place where sin ran rampant and virtue was all but forgotten.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resilient</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/Lore-History/backstory/resilient/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/Lore-History/backstory/resilient/</guid>
      <description>The world that The Resilient inhabits is a stark contrast to the one they once knew. The Dark Fever has not only claimed countless lives but also decimated infrastructure, technology, and society as a whole. As survivors of this devastating pandemic, The Resilient have found themselves in a precarious position – living amongst the remnants of a world that has all but crumbled around them.&#xA;In the aftermath of The Dark Fever, many families were torn apart, with children losing their parents and vice versa.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Synthetic Order</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/Lore-History/backstory/synthetic-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/Lore-History/backstory/synthetic-order/</guid>
      <description>The Synthetic Order was founded before The Dark Fever as a collaborative effort between engineers, scientists, and artificial intelligence (AI) to aid humanity in recovering from the devastation caused by a previous event. Initially, their primary mission involved developing intelligent machines capable of performing tasks too dangerous or time-consuming for humans. These creations focused on agriculture, resource extraction, healthcare, and education, helping to replenish the world&amp;rsquo;s depleted food supply and infrastructure while also providing advanced medical equipment and educational materials.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
